

Jonas Eriksson

- **** 070 420 01 75
- jonaseriksson84@gmail.com
- Pryggvägen 6B 117 71 Stockholm
- 😯 www.mynameisjonas.dev

I am a fullstack web developer with 10+ years of professional experience. I particularly enjoy doing frontend development and JavaScript, though also comfortable with backend and API development in a number of languages such as Python, Java and server-side JavaScript.

I am a social person and thrive in a strong team, but I am also full of initiative and drive – I will quickly learn new processes, environments and technologies on my own. Regardless of project, I always carry a professional attitude and clear focus on delivering results.

Frameworks:

React, Next.js, Svelte, Angular, Django, Node

Languages:

JavaScript, Python, HTML5, CSS3, Java, SQL

Databases:

postgres, MySQL, DB2

Tooling:

Jest, npm, pytest, Terraform, Webpack, Yarn

Version handling & CM:

Git, CVS, SVN, Confluence, JIRA

Other

AWS, Ansible, Docker, Jenkins, Linux, REST, Scrum, Vagrant

Swedish: Native English: Fluent

German: Basic proficiency **Italian** Basic proficiency **Japanese:** Basic proficiency

EXPERIENCE

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER / Reason Studios

October 2017 - present

- · Heavily involved in infrastructure and devops including build systems and servers/AWS
- Serving 10 000+ daily end users with always available systems
- Technical responsibility for the web shop, generating 75% of company revenue
- Technical responsibility for authentication and the license systems
- True full stack development from databases via APIs and microservices to frontend
- Quickly got up to speed in new frameworks Python & Django

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER (consultant) / Polisen (via HiQ)

June 2016 — October 2017

- Lead frontend developer porting COBOL systems to modern web-based applications
- Also included significant Java backend development
- · Deliverables finished far ahead of schedule
- Introduced the team to frontend build systems and testing

FRONTEND DEVELOPER (consultant) / Midroc (via HiQ)

October 2014 - June 2016

- · Lead frontend developer in multiple projects
- Large influence on UX and design decisions
- Introduced new technologies incl. AngularJS, Sharepoint APIs and Microsoft Graph
- Developed new intranet start page for 1100 employees and 70 000+ views/month
- Various other projects, including portals for project planning and time reporting

JAVA DEVELOPER (consultant) / Euroclear (via Capgemini)

February 2012 - August 2014

- Advanced from graduate to lead developer of the Java services within the first year
- Chosen to the 7 employee core team out of total 25 employees
- Responsible for estimation, analysis, bugfixing and documentation of incidents and change requests
- Project leader responsibilites for time plans, team briefings and client meetings
- Shared responisibility for new hires, including interviews, training and core reviews

EDUCATION

M.Sc. Industrial Engineering and Management (International, Japanese)

2005 — 2011

The Institute of Technology at Linköping University

- Computer science programming, computer architecture, larger project based software engineering courses.
- Industrial Marketing project management, strategic mangagement and positioning.
- Preceded by one year of Japanese courses

Exchange Studies

2008 — 2009

明治大学 / Meiji University, Tokyo

Exchange student programme as part of the masters degree. All courses were given in Japanese, and consisted of business and management courses.